OK. I'll tell him you called.
好的. 我会告诉他你来过电话.
Hey, that was Lisa.
Hey, 刚才是Lisa.
She said you were supposed to meet her.
她说你本来要跟她见面的.
I know. I was. Was she mad?
我知道. 我是要跟她见面. 她生气了吗?
Was she mad!
她生气了吗!
Oh boy, I blew it.
Oh boy, 我把一切搞砸了.
Well, she said she was going home and she'd call you later.
Well, 她说她要回家, 会再给你打电话.
What happened?
发生了什么事?
I taped in the Square this morning.
我今天上午在广场拍片.
Then I had a meeting over at school with my advisor.
然后去学校见了我的导师.
First of all, he was 45 minutes late.
首先, 他迟到了45分钟.
Then after a complete progress report, he decides to go over the whole project from the top.
接着, 在我做了完整的进度报告之后, 他决定要从头开始审查整个项目.
What a pain!
真是讨厌!
I wanted to just get up and walk out.
我当时就想起身走人.
Temper, Michael. He is your graduate advisor.
冷静, Michael. 他可是你的研究生导师.
Lisa will calm down.
Lisa会冷静下来的.
It's nothing a little gesture on your part won't fix.
你只需稍微表示表示就能补救这一切.
Ask her to marry you.
向她求婚吧.
Let's not go to extremes.
别走极端.
Tell her it'll never happen again.
向她保证再也不会发生这种事.
I told her that the last time.
我上次就跟她这么说过了.
Well well well, you do have a problem, don't you?
Well well well, 你确实碰到了难题, 是吧?
I could grovel.
我可以低声下气求她原谅.
Groveling is an option. Now, personally I don't grovel.
这也是一个办法. 就我个人而言, 我从不低声下气求人.
I just inspire women to break up with me.
我只会促使女人与我分手.
Maybe you should try groveling.
也许你应该试试低声下气.